John Alden Mason Papers 1904-1967 Mss.B.M384
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1926-1967; 20 linear feet
  - Rea, Joy, 1955; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Reading, Penna., Public Museum (Box 30)
    - Mengel, Levi W (Box 30)
  - Reagen, Albert B (Box 30)
  - Recinos, Adrián (Box 30)
  - Redfield, Robert (Box 30)
  - Reed, Erik K (Box 30)
  - Reeder, Katharine de (Box 30)
  - Reeves, Ruth (Box 30)
  - Regelin, Clinton (Box 30)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 30)
  - Regler, Margaret (Box 30)
  - Reich, John F (Box 30)
    - Jimerson, Abner (Box 30)
    - McHugh, Jane M (Box 30)
      re: Seneca Indian paintings of Sanford Plummer
  - Reichard, Gladys A (Box 30)
  - Reiche, Maria (Box 30)
  - Reichel-Dolmatoff, Gerardo (Box 30)
  - Reid, J. H (Box 30)
  - Reifler, Erwin (Box 30)
  - Reindollar, Eleanor L (Box 30)
  - Reisz, A Ch (Box 30)
  - Reiter, Murray (Box 30)
  - Reiter, Paul (Box 30)
  - Reko, B. P (Box 30)
    - Jayne, Horace (Box 30)
  - Reko, Victor A (Box 30)
  - Rendon, Francisco Huerta (Box 30)
  - Report of expedition to northern Mexico, 1935-1936 (Box 30)
  - Report on archaeological site, Madison Two, Vinton County, Ohio (Box 30)
  - Reports, abstracts, etc (Box 30)
  - Requena, Rafael (Box 30)
  - Respaldiza, José Ricardo (Box 30)
  - Review for Hewett's Ancient Life in the American Southwest. (Box 30)
  - Reviews and notes for Archaeology. (Box 30)
  - Reviews of books (2) on the Inca, 1954 (Box 30)
  - Revista Mexicana de Estudios Antropologicos (Box 30)
    - Christensen, Bodil (Box 30)
  - Reward for recovery of Mexican gold objects (Box 30)
  - Reyes Cancino, Manuel (Box 30)
  - Reygadas,Vértiz, José (Box 30)
  - Reymershoffer, Charles (Box 30)
    - Jayne, Horace (Box 30)
  - Reynolds, George (Box 30)
  - Rhode Island School of Design (Box 31)
    - Museum of Art (Box 31)
  - Ribera, Roberto, Jr (Box 31)
  - Riccio,Armand (Box 31)
  - Rice, Carlton C (Box 31)
  - Rices, Maurice (Box 31)
  - Rich, D W (Box 31)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 31)
  - Richards, H. A (Box 31)
  - Richards, Horace G (Box 31)
  - Richards, J. Stanley (Box 31)
  - Richardson, Francis B (Box 31)
  - Richardson, Juan (Box 31)
  - Richeson, A. W (Box 31)
  - Ricketson, Oliver, Jr (Box 31)
  - Ridge, Fred Hamilton (Box 31)
  - Riegel, Ella (Box 31)
  - Ries, Maurice (Box 31)
  - Riess-Vasquez, Mrs. E (Box 31)
  - Rife, Dwight W (Box 31)
  - Riggs, Mollie Hall (Box 31)
  - Righetti, Mrs. Olimpia L (Box 31)
  - Rights, Douglas L (Box 31)
  - Riley, Carroll L (Box 31)
    - McCord, John (Box 31)
  - Risley, H Masten (Box 31)
  - Ritchey, Edna Rogers (Box 31)
    - Clapp, Clifford Blake (Box 31)
    - Hertzog, Walter S (Box 31)
    - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 31)
    - Ritchey, Roger C (Box 31)
    - Robertson, James A (Box 31)
    - Spinden, Herbert J (Box 31)
    - Whitford, A C (Box 31)
  - Ritchey, Mrs. Rena Rogers (Box 31)
  - Ritchie, William A (Box 31)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 31)
  - Ritzenthaler, Robert E (Box 31)
  - Riva, Roger De (Box 31)
  - Rivas P., Enrique (Box 31)
  - Rivas, Raimundo (Box 31)
  - Rivera, Roberto R Jr (Box 31)
  - Rivet, Paul (Box 31)
  - Rivière, Georges Henri (Box 31)
  - Riviere, Georges Henri (Box 31)
  - Roach, James (Box 31)
  - Robbins, Maurice (Box 31)
  - Roberts, Frank H. H (Box 31)
  - Roberts, Harold E (Box 31)
  - Roberts, Helen H (Box 31)
  - Roberts, Henry (Box 31)
  - Roberts, Kimberley S (Box 31)
  - Robinson, David M (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Mrs. Ella (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Mrs. Florence N (Box 31)
  - Robinson, M Adelaide (Box 31)
    - Van Meter, I (Box 31)
  - Robles C, Humberto A (Box 31)
  - Robles, Vitalino (Box 31)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A (Box 31)
  - Rocker, R (Box 31)
  - Rodakiewicz, E (Box 31)
  - Rodas N., Flavio (Box 31)
  - Rodeck, Hugo G (Box 31)
  - Roed-Müller, C (Box 31)
  - Roestler, Herbert E (Box 31)
  - Roger Williams Park, Providence R.I (Box 31)
  - Rogers, Cameron (Box 31)
    - The Grace Log (Box 31)
  - Rogers, Charles Ross (Box 31)
  - Rogers, Edward S (Box 31)
  - Rogers, Malcolm J (Box 31)
  - Rogers, Natalie (Box 31)
    - Nichols, Henry W (Box 31)
  - Rohner, Mrs. Evelyn C (Box 31)
  - Rojas, A (Box 31)
  - Rolfes, F. J (Box 31)
  - Rollins, Thor A (Box 31)
  - Romer, Alfred S (Box 31)
  - Romera, Ramón (Box 31)
  - Roop, Wendell P (Box 31)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 31)
    - Pearsall, Leigh M (Box 31)
  - Roosa, William B (Box 31)
  - Root, William C (Box 31)
  - Rorer, J. T (Box 31)
  - Rose, David (Box 31)
  - Rose, Elizabeth Kirk (Box 31)
  - Rose, Margaret (Box 31)
  - Rosen, Bessie (Box 31)
  - Rosenberger, A F (Box 31)
  - Rosenthal, Earl (Box 31)
  - Rosenthal, Gertrude (Box 31)
  - Rosnev, Jere de (Box 31)
  - Ross, Evelyn Grace (Box 31)
  - Ross, Hunter (Box 31)
  - Ross, John H (Box 31)
  - Ross, Kip (Box 31)
  - Ross, M. W (Box 31)
  - Rossbach, Ildefonso (Box 31)
  - Roswell, Irving P (Box 31)
  - Roth-Lutra, Karl H (Box 31)
  - Rothrop, S E (Box 31)
  - Rotzel, Grace (Box 31)
  - Rougvie, H (Box 31)
  - Rouse, B Irving (Box 31)
  - Rouse, Irving (Box 31)
  - Rowe, John Howland, 1942-1955; 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Rowe, Leo S (Box 31)
  - Rowell, Mary (Box 31)
  - Royer, Russell J (Box 31)
  - Roys, Lawrence (Box 31)
  - Rubin de la Bordolla, Daniel F (Box 31)
  - Ruettinger, John W (Box 31)
  - Runge, Guido (Box 31)
  - Rusk, W. S (Box 31)
  - Russell, G Oscar (Box 31)
    - Bolling, George M (Box 31)
  - Rutledge, Archibald (Box 31)
  - Ruyle, John B (Box 31)
  - Ruz Lhuillier, Alberto (Box 32)
  - Ruz popular Palenque article, 1953 (Box 32)
  - Rybak, Shulamith (Box 32)
  - Ryden, Stig (Box 32)
  - S.P.A. Early years and Pennsylvania Indian Survey (Box 32)
  - S.P.A. New Constitution (Box 32)
  - Sabul, Bernard (Box 32)
  - Sahagian, Helen (Box 32)
  - Salaman, Redcliffe N (Box 32)
  - Saleski, R. E (Box 32)
  - Salter, L J (Box 32)
  - Salzmann, Zdenek (Box 32)
  - Samayoa Chinchilla, Carlos (Box 32)
  - Samuel, Ray (Box 32)
  - Sandford, Joseph E (Box 32)
  - Sandoval S, Luis (Box 32)
  - Santullano, Luis S (Box 32)
  - Sapir, Edward, 1914-1939; 2 folders (Box 32)
    Includes two letters, 1914, with extensive commentary on Mason's work on Uto-Aztecan languages, including Tepehuan and Tepecano.
  - Sapper, D. E (Box 32)
  - Sargent, Paul H (Box 32)
  - Sarkar, Marie D (Box 32)
  - Sasseville, Roland E (Box 32)
  - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr, 1933-1939; 7 folders (Box 32)
  - Satterthwaite expedition, 1953 (Box 32)
    - Beyer, Hermann (Box 32)
    - Blom, Dr (Box 32)
    - Jayne, Horace (Box 32)
    - Marquina, Ignacio (Box 32)
    - Satterthwaite, Peggy (Box 32)
    - Schellas, P (Box 32)
  - Satterthwaite, Willis H (Box 32)
  - Saturday Evening Post (Box 32)
    - Alexander, Jack (Box 32)
  - Sauer, Carl (Box 32)
  - Sault Daily Star (Box 32)
    - Curran, J W (Box 32)
  - Savage, M. F (Box 32)
  - Savage, Mrs. James (Box 32)
  - Savannah Evening Press (Box 32)
  - Saville, Marshall H (Box 32)
  - Sawyer, Alan R (Box 32)
  - Sawyer, Charles H (Box 32)
  - Sawyer, L. R (Box 32)
  - Sayles, E. B (Box 32)
  - Schaedel, Richard P (Box 33)
  - Schaefer, Vincent J (Box 33)
  - Schaeffer, Claude E (Box 33)
  - Schaeffer, Crozer (Box 33)
  - Schaeffer, George C (Box 33)
  - Schaeffer, Myron S (Box 33)
    - Erickson, Evelyn E (Box 33)
  - Scharff, Maurice R (Box 33)
  - Schellas, Paul (Box 33)
  - Schellhous, P (Box 33)
  - Schembs, Roger (Box 33)
  - Schenone, John F (Box 33)
  - Schepotieff, A (Box 33)
  - Schertel, Ernst (Box 33)
  - Schiedt, R. C (Box 33)
  - Schiek, Martha J (Box 33)
  - Schindler, Robert (Box 33)
  - Schlesinger, Ana María (Box 33)
  - Schmaus, Francis T (Box 33)
  - Schmaus, Frank (Box 33)
  - Schneider, Walther F (Box 33)
  - Schnert, Marion P (Box 33)
  - Schnohr, Peter (Box 33)
  - Schoeler, Walram V, von (Box 33)
  - Schoenstedt, E (Box 33)
  - Schoff, Harry L (Box 33)
  - Scholastic (Box 33)
    - Watson, Ernest W (Box 33)
  - Scholl, Robert P (Box 33)
  - Schoonover, Frank E (Box 33)
  - Schoonover, Ruth C (Box 33)
  - Schreeder, Hugo (Box 33)
  - Schroerer, Federico (Box 33)
  - Schuller, Rudolf (Box 33)
  - Schultz, Tom W (Box 33)
  - Schumann, Edward A., Jr (Box 33)
  - Schuster, Carl (Box 33)
  - Schutt, Marie E (Box 33)
  - Schwab, William B (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Douglas W (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Ray (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Stuart (Box 33)
  - Science (Box 33)
    - Dees, Sarah (Box 33)
  - Science League of America (Box 33)
  - Science Press Printing Co (Box 33)
  - Science Service, Inc (Box 33)
    - Davis, Emily C (Box 33)
    - Davis, Watson (Box 33)
  - Scientific Monthly (Box 33)
    - Cattell, Ware (Box 33)
  - Scofield, John K (Box 33)
  - Scott, Andrew (Box 33)
  - Scott, Catherine S (Box 33)
  - Scott, Donald (Box 33)
  - Sea Island Co (Box 33)
    - Compton, J. D (Box 33)
  - Searcy, Elizabeth (Box 33)
  - Searle, H E (Box 33)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Co (Box 33)
  - Sebeok, Thomas A (Box 33)
  - Seder, Theodore A (Box 33)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 33)
    - Herzog, George (Box 33)
    - Voegelin, Erminie (Box 33)
    - Voegelin, Carl (Box 33)
  - Sedlak, Rosa (Box 33)
  - Seeger, Charles (Box 33)
  - Seeman, E. A (Box 33)
  - Sehmans, Frank (Box 33)
  - Sehnert, Marion P (Box 33)
  - Seifriz, William (Box 33)
  - Selestow, John A (Box 33)
  - Sellards, E. H (Box 33)
  - Selle, Mrs. Emilio (Box 33)
  - Sellers, Charles Coleman (Box 33)
  - Selsor, Mark A (Box 33)
  - Selvidge, R. B (Box 33)
  - Sepulveda de Schoneman, Florencia (Box 33)
  - Serrano, Antonio (Box 33)
  - Sessler, Robert G G (Box 33)
  - Settles, O (Box 33)
  - Setzler, Frank M (Box 33)
    - Judd, Neil M (Box 33)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 33)
  - Sevy, C R (Box 33)
  - Sewall, Alice M (Box 33)
  - Seyrig, Henri (Box 33)
  - Shafer, Robert (Box 33)
  - Shank, Thomas A (Box 33)
  - Shanlis, Edward A (Box 33)
  - Shannon, Edward J (Box 33)
  - Shapiro, Harry L (Box 33)
    - Weitzner, Bella (Box 33)
  - Sharfman, Herbert (Box 33)
  - Sharpless, William (Box 33)
  - Shattuck, Floyd E (Box 33)
  - Shattuck, George Cheever (Box 33)
  - Shaver, I. H (Box 33)
  - [Shaw], Alden (Box 33)
  - Shelby, C Levi (Box 33)
  - Shelby, Charmion (Box 33)
  - Sheldon, Mrs. Irene R (Box 33)
  - Shelly, Rebecca Roberts (Box 33)
  - Shenk, Mrs. Priscilla Fansler (Box 33)
  - Shenk, Priscilla (Box 33)
  - Shepherd, Anna O (Box 33)
  - Sherman, Virginia (Box 33)
  - Shertone, Henry C (Box 33)
  - Sherwood, Arthur (Box 33)
  - Shetrone, H C (Box 33)
  - Shevin, Ruth (Box 33)
  - Shick, Augustus W (Box 33)
  - Shimkin, Demitri (Box 33)
  - Shinkin, Demitri B (Box 33)
  - Shirley, Paul (Box 33)
  - Shoemaker, Richard (Box 33)
  - Shook, Edwin M (Box 33)
  - Short, Charles A (Box 33)
  - Shotridge, Louis (Box 33)
  - Shreve, Marvin D (Box 33)
  - Shufelt, P W (Box 33)
  - Shuster [Schuster?], Karl (Box 33)
  - Siebert, Frank T (Box 33)
  - Simkhovitch, Vladimir G (Box 33)
  - Simmons, Thomas W (Box 33)
  - Simms, S. C (Box 33)
  - Simo˜es de Paula, Euripides (Box 33)
  - Simons, David G (Box 33)
  - Simons, Katherine W (Box 33)
  - Simpson, George E (Box 33)
  - Simpson, Ruth D (Box 33)
  - Singer, Ernestine W (Box 33)
  - Sinkler, Miss (Box 33)
  - Siple, E W (Box 33)
  - Sisters Store (Box 33)
  - Skinner, Dorothy (Box 34)
  - Slavens, S G (Box 34)
  - Slavin, Clifford (Box 34)
  - Slavin, Mary E (Box 34)
  - Sloan, William S (Box 34)
  - Sloane, William (Box 34)
  - Slotkin, J S (Box 34)
  - Smiley, Terah L (Box 34)
  - Smith, Arthur (Box 34)
    - Stirling, Matthew W (Box 34)
  - Smith, Curtis H (Box 34)
  - Smith, Earl C (Box 34)
  - Smith, G. Hubert (Box 34)
  - Smith, Harlan I (Box 34)
  - Smith, Hobart M (Box 34)
  - Smith, Isabel (Box 34)
  - Smith, Lynn (Box 34)
  - Smith, Margaret R (Box 34)
  - Smith, Marian W (Box 34)
  - Smith, Marion (Box 34)
    - Wi e, Joyce (Box 34)
  - Smith, Mr & Mrs Robert Eliot (Box 34)
  - Smith, Mrs. Harrison (Box 34)
  - Smith, Nicholas N (Box 34)
  - Smith, Portia H. B (Box 34)
  - Smith, Ray W (Box 34)
  - Smith, Robert A (Box 34)
  - Smith, Robert C., Jr (Box 34)
  - Smith, Robert E (Box 34)
  - Smith, William T (Box 34)
  - Smithsonian Institution to Cocle, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Smithsonian Institution (Box 34)
    - Beals, Ralph L (Box 34)
    - Abbot, C. G (Box 34)
    - Carter, Ethelwyn (Box 34)
    - Fenton, William N (Box 34)
    - Judd, Neil M (Box 34)
    - Oehser, Paul H (Box 34)
    - Palmer, M Helen (Box 34)
    - Roberts, Frank H H Jr (Box 34)
    - Steward, Julian H (Box 34)
    - Stirling, Matthew W (Box 34)
  - Smolleck, Howard A (Box 34)
  - Snively, Donald L (Box 34)
  - Snowden, Margaret (Box 34)
  - Snowdon, C. L., Jr (Box 34)
  - Snowdon, Mrs. C L., Jr (Box 34)
  - Snowdon, Ruth J (Box 34)
  - Snyder, Edgar C (Box 34)
  - Social Science Abstracts (Box 34)
    - Chapin, F Stuart (Box 34)
    - Dewey, Virginia (Box 34)
    - Hosea, Harold R (Box 34)
    - Kenny, Lily (Box 34)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 34)
    - Barrett, Laura (Box 34)
    - Petrullo, Vincenzo (Box 34)
    - Whorf, Benjamin L (Box 34)
    - Wilbur, Walter Karl (Box 34)
  - Sociedad Colombista Panamericana (Box 34)
    - Castells, J Martínez (Box 34)
  - Society for American Archeology., 1941-1949 (Box 34)
    - Black, Glenn A (Box 34)
    - Byers, Douglas S (Box 34)
    - Deuel, Thorne (Box 34)
    - Ekholm, Gordon F (Box 34)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 34)
    - Griffin, James B (Box 34)
    - Guthe, Carl E (Box 34)
    - Haury, Emil W (Box 34)
    - Herskovits, Melville J (Box 34)
    - Johnson, Frederick (Box 34)
    - Judd, Neil M (Box 34)
    - Macgowan, Kenneth (Box 34)
    - McKern, W C (Box 34)
    - Nelson, N C (Box 34)
    - Noquera, Eduardo (Box 34)
    - Parker, Arthur C (Box 34)
    - Quimby, George (Box 34)
    - Revised Constitution (Box 34)
    - Richardson, Mr. & Mrs. Edward Bridge (Box 34)
    - Richardson, Helen Langdon (Box 34)
    - Roberts, Frank H H J (Box 34)
    - Setzler, Frank M (Box 34)
    - Shapiro, Harry (Box 34)
    - Stewart, T D (Box 34)
    - Strong, William Duncan (Box 34)
    - Wedel, Waldo R (Box 34)
    - Willett, Evelyn (Box 34)
  - Society for Applied Anthropology (Box 34)
    - Purcell, Elizabeth (Box 34)
  - Society for Pennsylvania Archeology (Box 34)
  - Society for Pennsylvania Archeology (Box 34)
    - Acker, Lewis F (Box 34)
    - Brooks, Seal T (Box 34)
    - Byers, Douglas S (Box 34)
    - Cadzow, Donald A (Box 34)
    - Carpenter, Edmund S (Box 34)
    - Davis, C Vernoy (Box 34)
    - Deardorff, M H (Box 34)
    - Dorrance, Frances (Box 34)
    - Eckman, D J (Box 34)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 34)
    - Kuhns, Miriam (Box 34)
    - Light, Richard (Box 34)
    - Linker, Frank V (Box 34)
    - Luce, Stephen B (Box 34)
    - Mrozoski, Vincent R (Box 34)
    - Roberts, Ruth E (Box 34)
    - Schaeffer, Claude E (Box 34)
    - Streeper, Edwena W (Box 34)
    - Swauger, James L (Box 34)
    - Taylor, Walter W Jr (Box 34)
    - Upham, Donald B (Box 34)
    - Witthoft, John (Box 34)
    - Wright, Richard (Box 34)
  - Society of the Sigma Xi (Box 34)
    - Hutchinson, W G (Box 34)
    - Sandback, Helen K (Box 34)
  - Soday, Frank J (Box 34)
  - Sole i Pla, Joan (Box 34)
  - Solecki, Dolores Nourse (Box 34)
  - Solenberger, Robert Reeves (Box 34)
    - Albert Teachers' Agency (Box 34)
    - Morgan, Kenneth (Box 34)
  - Sologuren, Mercedes (Box 34)
  - Solosth, R E (Box 34)
  - Sonin, Robert (Box 34)
  - Sontag, L W (Box 34)
  - Soper, Ellis (Box 34)
  - Soule, Phelps (Box 34)
    - Eiseley, Loren C (Box 34)
  - Source Research Council, Inc (Box 34)
    - Davis, Warren (Box 34)
    - Knight, F G (Box 34)
  - South American Handbook., 1939-1947 (Box 34)
    - Carter, Ethelwyn E (Box 34)
    - Garro, J Eugenio (Box 34)
    - Levin, Leon L (Box 34)
    - Métraux, A (Box 34)
    - Rivet, Paul (Box 34)
    - Steward, Julian H (Box 34)
    - Willey, Gordon R (Box 34)
  - South Australia, Public Library, Museum, and Art Gallery of (Box 34)
    - Hale, Herbert M (Box 34)
  - Southern Pacific Lines (Box 34)
  - Southwest Museum (Box 34)
    - Amsden, Charles (Box 34)
    - Brainerd, George W (Box 34)
  - Spaeth, Carl B (Box 35)
  - Spear, Mrs. Franklin B (Box 35)
  - Speck, Frank G (Box 35)
    - Speck, Florence (Box 35)
  - Spect, Gustavo (Box 35)
  - Spellmeyer, S A (Box 35)
  - Spence, G. H (Box 35)
  - Spencer, C (Box 35)
    - Jayne, Horace (Box 35)
  - Spencer, Dorothy (Box 35)
  - Spencer, Steven M (Box 35)
  - Sperb, Jane (Box 35)
  - Spewak, Ben (Box 35)
  - Spicer, Edward H (Box 35)
  - Spier, Leslie (Box 35)
  - Spigelman, Joseph H (Box 35)
  - Spiller, J. L (Box 35)
  - Spinden, H. J (Box 35)
    - Wetmore, Alexander (Box 35)
  - Spindler, George D (Box 35)
  - Spink and Son, Ltd (Box 35)
  - Splinter, Leonard (Box 35)
  - Spoehr, Alexander (Box 35)
  - Spofford, Ernest (Box 35)
  - St. Louis. City Art Museum (Box 35)
  - Stafiey, Chester (Box 35)
  - Stallings, W S., Jr (Box 35)
  - Standard Fruit and Steamship Co (Box 35)
  - Stanford, R. C (Box 35)
  - Stanford, Richard B (Box 35)
  - Staples, Doris M (Box 35)
  - A State Archaeological Survey (Box 35)
  - Stearns, F. A (Box 35)
  - Stechert, G. E. & Co (Box 35)
  - Steck, Jack (Box 35)
  - Stecker, A (Box 35)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur (Box 35)
  - Steger, Elena (Box 35)
  - Steggerda, Morris (Box 35)
  - Stehdahl, Alfred E (Box 35)
  - Stein, C L W (Box 35)
  - Steinmetz, Gus M (Box 35)
  - Stelle, Albert (Box 35)
  - Stendahl, Earl L (Box 35)
  - Stephens, Mrs. D. Owen (Box 35)
  - Stephens, Mrs. Lucie L (Box 35)
  - Stephens, S. G (Box 35)
  - Stern, Theodore (Box 35)
  - Stevens, Edmund W (Box 35)
  - Stevens, Sylvester K (Box 35)
  - Stevenson, Miss (Box 35)
  - Stevenson, Allan A (Box 35)
  - Stevenson, Robert (Box 35)
  - Stevenson, William H (Box 35)
  - Steward, Elizabeth (Box 36)
  - Steward, Julian H (Box 36)
    - Heyser Espinosa, Ramón (Box 36)
  - Stewart, T. Dale (Box 36)
  - Stewart, T. B (Box 36)
  - Stice, R. L (Box 36)
  - Stiles, Mary Hatch (Box 36)
  - Stimson, Anna K (Box 36)
  - Stimson, J Frank (Box 36)
  - Stirling, Matthew W (Box 36)
    - Gall, August Freiherr v (Box 36)
  - Stites, Raymond S (Box 36)
  - Stokes, Frances J (Box 36)
  - Stokes, William E (Box 36)
  - Stoll, J. Westbrook (Box 36)
  - Stoller, Marianne (Box 36)
  - Stone, Doris Z (Box 36)
  - Stone, Mrs. Doris (Box 36)
  - Storm, Paul J (Box 36)
  - Storms, Garnet R (Box 36)
    - McHugh, J M (Box 36)
  - Stout, David B., 1942-1956 (Box 36)
  - Stradvene, Adolph (Box 36)
  - Stratford Co (Box 36)
  - Strawbridge, Francis (Box 36)
  - Strawn, Dan D (Box 36)
  - Streeper, E W (Box 36)
  - Streusser-Pean, Guy (Box 36)
  - Strobel, Mazie (Box 36)
  - Strohmeier, William (Box 36)
  - Strong, William Duncan (Box 36)
  - Strong,William W (Box 36)
  - Strother, W. M (Box 36)
  - Strunk, Orlo, Jr (Box 36)
    - Peterson, Frederick A (Box 36)
  - Stubbs, Stanley (Box 36)
  - Studer, Floyd V (Box 36)
  - Sturtevant, Edgar H (Box 36)
  - Sturtevant, William C (Box 36)
  - Suarez, Rafael A (Box 36)
    - Caulfield, James T (Box 36)
  - Suarez, Rodolfo A (Box 36)
  - Subber, Josephine (Box 36)
  - Sud (Box 36)
  - Sun Oil Co (Box 36)
  - Supernaw, J S (Box 36)
  - Sutherland, William M (Box 36)
    - Angell, William R (Box 36)
  - Sutter, Charles (Box 36)
  - Swadesh, Morris, 1941-1962 (Box 36)
  - Swain, Frank K (Box 36)
  - Swain, J E (Box 36)
  - Swanton, John R (Box 36)
  - Swauger, James L (Box 36)
  - Swenson, Merrill G (Box 36)
  - Swientochowski, John (Box 36)
  - Szweda, Stefana (Box 36)
  - Taft Museum (Box 36)
    - Hanna, Katherine (Box 36)
    - Rainey, Froelich Gladstone (Box 36)
  - Talk given before Soc. Geog. Hist., Guatemala, (English), June 1938 (Box 36)
  - Talley, Harry S (Box 36)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 36)
  - Tanaka, Joseph K (Box 36)
  - Tannenbaum, Frank (Box 36)
  - Tantaquidgeon, Gladys (Box 36)
  - Tarrington, R. C (Box 36)
  - Tate, Harry L (Box 36)
  - Tatelman, Edward I P (Box 36)
    - Rainey, Froelich G (Box 36)
  - Tatten, David K (Box 36)
  - Tatum, R M (Box 36)
  - Tatum, Robert (Box 36)
  - Tax, Sol (Box 36)
  - Taylor Museum, Colorado Springs, Colorado (Box 36)
  - Taylor, Carolyn (Box 36)
  - Taylor, Griffiths (Box 36)
  - Taylor, Jay L. B (Box 36)
  - Taylor, Walter W., Jr (Box 36)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 36)
  - Taylor, William P (Box 36)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (Box 36)
    - Lawlor, J J (Box 36)
    - Shirley, JeanM (Box 36)
  - Tejeda F., Antonio (Box 36)
  - Telfair, Margery W (Box 36)
  - Tellez, Manuel C (Box 36)
  - Tello, Julio C (Box 36)
  - Temperly, N Ridley (Box 36)
  - Tenz, Oscar (Box 36)
  - Tepehuan & Pima Bajo Recordings (Box 36)
    - Brugge, David M (Box 36)
  - Tepehuan of northern Mexico (Box 36)
  - Termer, Franz (Box 36)
  - Termer, Franz (Box 36)
    - Kidder, Alfred (Box 36)
    - Linné, Siguald (Box 36)
    - Rothfritz, Thre (?) Margarita (Box 36)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 36)
  - Terra, Helmut da (Box 37)
  - Terry, Roland (Box 37)
  - Texas Archeological and Paleontological Society (Box 37)
    - Holden, W C (Box 37)
  - Thayer Ojeda, Luis (Box 37)
  - The Maya (Box 37)
  - The Memorial Art Gallery (Box 37)
    - Vaughn, Jessie (Box 37)
  - The Museum of Modern Art (Box 37)
  - The Peruvians (Box 37)
  - The Telegraph Press (Box 37)
  - Think Magazine (Box 37)
  - Thomas, Charles C (Box 37)
  - Thomas, Irving O (Box 37)
  - Thomas, Ruth C (Box 37)
  - Thomas, W. Stephan (Box 37)
  - Thomas, Wilbur K (Box 37)
    - Wilbur, Walter K (Box 37)
  - Thomas, William L., Jr (Box 37)
  - Thomas, Winifred (Box 37)
  - Thomen, Luis F (Box 37)
  - Thomlinson, M H (Box 37)
  - Thomlinson, M. H (Box 37)
  - Thompson, C. Seymour (Box 37)
  - Thompson, Charles S (Box 37)
  - Thompson, Elizabeth (Box 37)
  - Thompson, J. Eric S (Box 37)
  - Thompson, M. Mason (?) Dutton (Box 37)
  - Thompson, Martha (Box 37)
  - Thompson, Nora B (Box 37)
  - Thompson, Raymond L (Box 37)
  - Thomson, J Monroe (Box 37)
  - Thomson, Thomas (Box 37)
  - Thord-Gray, I (Box 37)
    - Garrett, William A (Box 37)
  - Thornburgh, Richard A (Box 37)
  - Thornbury, Charlotte (Box 37)
  - Thorne, Robert C (Box 37)
  - Thorp, Willard (Box 37)
  - Thorpe, J. F (Box 37)
  - Thunderbird Museum (Box 37)
  - Thurnwald, R (Box 37)
  - Thurston, Bertha P (Box 37)
  - Tiedemann, Heinrich (Box 37)
  - Tillotson, R. W (Box 37)
  - Time, Ind (Box 37)
    - Bishop, Dorothy W (Box 37)
    - Northwood, Arthur Jr (Box 37)
    - Pratt, Francis Dew (Box 37)
    - Rich, Williston (Box 37)
  - Tioga Point Museum (Box 37)
  - Todd, Carmen C Vela de (Box 37)
    - Daniels, Josephus (Box 37)
    - Hughes, Morris N (Box 37)
    - Todd, Milton C (Box 37)
  - Todd, M. C (Box 37)
  - Todd, T. Wingate (Box 37)
  - Toledo Museum of Art (Box 37)
  - Toledo, J Everardo (Box 37)
  - Tolstoy, Paul (Box 37)
  - Tomkins, William (Box 37)
  - Tompkins, Lionel (Box 37)
  - Tooker, Helen (Box 37)
  - Toor, Frances (Box 37)
  - Toothaker, Charles R (Box 37)
    - Rodriguez, Rómulo Valerio (Box 37)
  - Torii, Midori (Box 37)
  - Torrey, Mrs. Raymond A (Box 37)
  - Toscano, Lic. Salvador (Box 37)
  - Totem Poles (Box 37)
  - Totten, George Oakley, Jr (Box 37)
  - Touring Bureau, Auto Club (Box 37)
  - Tovar, Antonio (Box 37)
    - Llausas, A. Lopez (Box 37)
  - Towle, Mrs. Margaret A (Box 37)
  - Townsend, John W., Jr (Box 37)
  - Townsend, W. Cameron (Box 37)
  - Tozzer, Alfred M (Box 37)
  - Traeger, Dorothy S (Box 37)
  - Travel Magazine (Box 37)
  - Travers, Roy (Box 37)
  - Travis, Robert (Box 37)
  - Tredyffrin-Easttown History Club Quarterly (Box 37)
    - Johnson, Mr (Box 37)
  - Trenner, Lew (Box 37)
  - Trevino (Box 37)
  - Trevino, Fausto (Box 37)
  - Trik, Aubrey S (Box 37)
  - Trout, William A (Box 37)
  - True, Rodney H (Box 37)
  - True Magazine (Box 37)
    - Rae, William (Box 37)
  - Trumbull, Mrs. Marjorie R. S (Box 37)
  - Tschiry, Leopold Robert (Box 37)
    - Barbancho, Fernando (Box 37)
    - Barrera Vasquez, Alfredo (Box 37)